

### CONTACT

### **Address**

236, Sai Shraddh Palace, Indore

#### **Phone**

+91 9977696202

#### **Email**

indrapal.singh1137@gmail.com

### **SKILLS**

HTML 5

CSS<sub>3</sub>

**Tailwind css** 

**Bootstrap** 

Js

**jQuery** 

**Photoshop** 

**Figma** 

Adobe Xd

React UI

## **INDRAPAL SINGH JATAV**

# Sr. Web Designer

## **ABOUT ME**

I have 4 years of experience in Web & UI/UX Designer. I am always looking for self-improvement with new possibilities. In rapid and structured progression in the management of my work perseverance and leadership is the primary reason. My design style is clean, professional, and quick.

Every unique creation starts from imagination, followed by dedication. I worked in a challenging environment with honesty and commitment with a determination to apply my knowledge, skills and experience, and professional aptitudes for the organization's success.

## **Portfolio**

https://indrapal1137.github.io/portfolio

### **EXPERIENCE**

Healthcare Informatics Pvt Ltd Sr. Web Designer	2023 - Present
<b>Hiecor Software Technologies Pvt Ltd</b> Sr. UI Engineer	2022 - 2023
Creative Thoughts Informatics Services Pvt Ltd Web Designer	2021-2022
Brainware Infosoft Web designer	2020-2021
JIT Inspire Web designer	2019-2020
Shiva Concept Solution Business Development Manager & Trainer	2015-2019
NIIT Indore Business Development Manager & Trainer	2010-2013

## **EDUCATION**

Lord Krishna College of Technology Master of Business Administration (HR/IT)	2020-2023
Govt. Arts and Commerce College Indore Bacholer in arts	2018-2020
NIIT Delhi	2008-2011

Professional Diploma in Software Engineering (GNIIT)